magneticone.com 2012-10-05

# osCommerce modules, X-Cart modules, CRE Loaded modules, Zen Cart modules

(last updated December 2010)

MagneticOne is committed to protecting your privacy.  

## Collection of Your Personal Information

At some MagneticOne sites, we ask you to provide personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address, or telephone number. We may also collect demographic information, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites. If you choose to make a purchase or sign up for a paid subscription service, we will ask for additional information, such as your credit card number and billing address, which is used to create a MagneticOne billing account.

Additionally, we collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring Web site addresses.  

## Use of Your Personal Information

MagneticOne collects and uses your personal information to operate and improve its sites and services.

We also use your personal information to communicate with you. We may send certain mandatory service communications such as welcome letters, billing reminders, information on technical service issues, and security announcements.   

## Cookies

MagneticOne utilizes cookies (small pieces of data stored by your Web browser on your hard drive) to offer you more personal and customized service. Most Web browsers accept cookies by default, but if you choose not to accept them, you can simply change your browser settings.  

## Collection of Anonymous Usage Statistics

MagneticOne reserves the right to gather information regarding the use of it's software and by installing the software, you grant MagneticOne permission to collect this information.

This does not include any personal information, such as who you are or your email address. We use this data to improve our software and develop a better product that meets your needs. 

## Sharing of Your Personal Information

Except as described in this statement, we will not disclose your personal information outside of MagneticOne and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your consent.  

## Changing Your Personal Information

You're free to change your personal information. Please note, that your email is used as unique identifier. You should notify MagneticOne if you'd like to have it changed, as it may require some additional actions from our side.

## Changes to This Privacy Statement

We will occasionally update this privacy statement to reflect changes in our services and customer feedback. When we post changes to this Statement, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this statement. If there are material changes to this statement or in how MagneticOne will use your personal information, we will notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes prior to implementing the change or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how MagneticOne is protecting your information.  

## Contacting Us

MagneticOne welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you have questions about this statement or believe that we have not adhered to it, please contact us by using our Web form. If you have a technical or general support question, please visit http://support.magneticone.com to learn more about MagneticOne support resources.
